const quizData = [
    // 33
    { question: "What is a characteristic of the LLC sublayer?", answers: ["It places information in the frame that allows multiple Layer 3 protocols to use the same network interface and media.", "It provides the logical addressing required that identifies the device.", "It is responsible for media access control.", "It provides delimitation of data according to the physical signaling requirements of the medium."], correct: "It places information in the frame that allows multiple Layer 3 protocols to use the same network interface and media." },
    // 11
    { question: "What is the purpose of the Cisco IOS command “show ip interface brief”?", answers: ["to display the routing table", "to display the ARP table", "to display the status of the router interfaces and their IP addresses", "to display the MAC address table"], correct: "to display the status of the router interfaces and their IP addresses" },
    // 48
    { question: "Which command can be used on a Windows PC to see the IP configuration of that computer?", answers: ["show ip interface brief", "ping", "ipconfig", "show interfaces"], correct: "ipconfig" },
    // 32
    { question: "What is a characteristic of the UTP cabling?", answers: ["The UTP cable is not susceptible to EMI or RFI.", "The UTP cable relies on the cancellation effect produced by the twisted wire pairs to limit signal degradation.", "The UTP cable is the most expensive type of LAN cabling.", "Each pair of wires is wrapped in metallic foil."], correct: "The UTP cable relies on the cancellation effect produced by the twisted wire pairs to limit signal degradation." },
    // 142
    { question: "Which protocol is used by the traceroute command to send and receive echo-requests and echo-replies?", answers: ["ICMP", "SNMP", "Telnet", "TCP"], correct: "ICMP" },
    // 42
    { question: "Which device performs the function of determining the path that messages should take through internetworks?", answers: ["a router", "a switch", "a hub", "a DSL modem"], correct: "a router" },
    // 28
    { question: "During the encapsulation process, what occurs at the data link layer for a PC connected to an Ethernet network?", answers: ["The logical address is added.", "The process port number is added.", "A frame is generated.", "Frames are converted to bits."], correct: "A frame is generated." },
    // 37
    { question: "What are two characteristics of IP? (Choose two.)", answers: ["does not require a dedicated end-to-end connection", "retransmits packets if they are lost", "reassembles out-of-order packets into the correct order at the destination", "operates independently of the network media", "guarantees delivery of packets"], correct: ["does not require a dedicated end-to-end connection", "operates independently of the network media"] },
    // 35
    { question: "What is an advantage of using a client-server model?", answers: ["A dedicated server is not required.", "Security is easier to manage.", "It does not require specialized network administration skills.", "All data is stored on the client devices."], correct: "Security is easier to manage." },
    // 8
    { question: "A company has a file server that provides services to the internal employees. What type of network does the company have?", answers: ["an intranet", "an extranet", "the internet", "a Moodle"], correct: "an intranet" },
];